Hostile Takeover is a action, comedy, thriller film
directed by Michael Hamilton-Wright.
Follows Pete, a professional hitman, as he faces a group of assassins after the boss of a crime
syndicate suspects disloyalty due to his attendance at Workaholics Anonymous meetings.
Pete, played by Michael Jai White.
Mora, played by Aimee Stolte.
Angel, played by Dawn Olivieri.
Reaper, played by Aleks Paunovic.
Muerto, played by Benjamin Joel Arcé.
Mingjue, played by Alex Mallari Jr..
David is a 2025 animated biblical musical film featuring the character
of David from the Book of Samuel in the Old Testament.
The film stars Phil Wickham, Brandon Engman, Asim Chaudhry, Miri Mesika,
Mick Wingert, Will de Renzy-Martin, and Lauren Daigle.
It is a follow-up to the five-part television miniseries Young David and tells the story of a young
Israelite shepherd, poet and warrior who is predestined to become the new King of Israel.
He embarks on a journey from beyond the shadow of an evil Philistine giant named Goliath to prove
to his people that true power lies not in a kingship but in faith and freedom.
David was released in theaters in the United States on
December 19, 2025, by Angel Studios.
The film received mostly positive reviews from critics and grossed $81 million.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.